and today is the sixty-third day
Post Juninho
because you're not following me there
Come on baby
Let's do that
ran out of truffles here Dude
so I'll fuel it again
27 days left for me to set up 1 business
and I need to make money
uncle us
is
sir
morale at the Cocoa Show
separated for me
free coffee
then I'll fill up the places and I'll do it
invitation from my event got
I have already rented 1 lot of chairs
inviting 1 lot of people we will see mano tiamo torcer
there
how are you
I'm fine and you pray
opa where is Milene
that's all good for me
it's there in Minas
I didn't know
Milene is not here
It's not in Minas
she went to BH
I'm going to do an event
and then I invite you
but i don't know what time you guys close
we are not
I only ask for the name of who will
just so I can come up with an idea of a space chair
you can't go
what a pity dear
there guys
I got here now at the thrift store
only the owner wasn't here man
she is traveling
wet vei
and then mandala
oh it doesn't
will not
you have no way to react
so no
I've already invited everyone bro
then I already ordered chair
I've done a lot of things
is on
either we make it happen or it's gone
but let's go let's be optimistic right crazy
I won't be suffering ahead of time
And mama ain't around